Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]
=The Maid=
=الخادمة=
=Episode 6=
=الحلقة 6=
No more escaping.
لا مزيد من الهروب.
Got you now.
لقد حصلت عليك الآن.
Just give it a try.
فقط جربه .
Try it.
جربها.
Let go!
اتركه!
Let me go.
دعني أذهب.
Try it.
جربها.
Open the door!
افتح الباب!
Lady Jifu is attacking the Princess Consort!
السيدة جيفو تهاجم الأميرة الزوجة!
Someone help!
ساعدوني يا أحد!
Let go of me!
أتركني!
Lady Jifu.
سيدة جيفو.
Lady Jifu, this is the Princess Consort!
السيدة جيفو، هذه هي الأميرة القرينة!
(Shen Yuanjin, Lin Jifu became like this because of you.)
(شين يوانجين، لين جيفو أصبحا هكذا بسببك.)
(You sowed the evil seed.)
(لقد زرعت البذرة الشريرة.)
(Now you shall reap the bitter harvest.)
(والآن سوف تحصد الحصاد المرير.)
Lady Jifu, release her now.
السيدة جيفو، أطلق سراحها الآن.
Wake up, Lady Jifu.
استيقظي يا سيدتي جيفو.
Someone help!
ساعدوني يا أحد!
Lady Jifu, this is the Princess Consort!
السيدة جيفو، هذه هي الأميرة القرينة!
Shen Yuanjin,
شين يوانجين،
how dare you hit me?
كيف تجرؤ على ضربي؟
Confiscate all the euphoria powder!
مصادرة كل مسحوق النشوة!
No more usage until the banquet!
لن يتم الاستخدام بعد الآن حتى موعد المأدبة!
- You... - Understood.
- أنت... - فهمت.
I warned you.
لقد حذرتك.
Ye Xiyan is no longer the Shen Yuqing
لم يعد Ye Xiyan هو Shen Yuqing
who bowed low and suffered humiliation.
الذين انحنوا وعانوا من الإذلال.
Snap out of your delusions.
تخلص من أوهامك.
Stop being her puppet.
توقف عن كونك دميتها.
Hypocrite.
منافق.
You only know how to play
أنت تعرف فقط كيفية اللعب
the docile little wife before Pei Ji.
الزوجة الصغيرة المطيعة أمام باي جي.
Aren't you tired?
هل أنت متعب؟
After the ladies' banquet,
بعد مأدبة السيدات،
I'll fulfill you wish.
سأحقق لك أمنيتك.
You'll be the capital's noblest lady.
سوف تكونين السيدة الأكثر نبلًا في العاصمة.
receiving the Empress Dowager's honors.
تلقي تكريمات الإمبراطورة الأرملة.
Who needs that?
من يحتاج ذلك؟
After the ladies' banquet,
بعد مأدبة السيدات،
you'll be married off to Jiangnan.
سيتم زواجك من جيانجنان.
We all want you to have a glorious wedding.
نحن جميعا نريد لك حفل زفاف رائع.
These few days,
في هذه الأيام القليلة،
just behave obediently.
فقط تصرف بطاعة.
Once in Jiangnan,
مرة واحدة في جيانغنان،
your husband's family will rely on your connections.
ستعتمد عائلة زوجك على علاقاتك.
You won't need to act so restrained like in the capital.
لن تحتاج إلى التصرف بضبط كما هو الحال في العاصمة.
Today, His Highness
اليوم صاحب السمو
will cast her aside.
سوف يلقيها جانبا.
Your Highness, you normally
صاحب السمو، أنت عادة
toil with state affairs.
العمل في شؤون الدولة.
Only after the winter hunt each year
فقط بعد صيد الشتاء كل عام
does the household reunite joyfully.
هل يجتمع أفراد الأسرة بفرح؟
We
نحن
shouldn't just enjoy your fine wine
لا ينبغي أن تستمتع فقط بالنبيذ الجيد
and fresh meat,
واللحوم الطازجة،
but must showcase
ولكن يجب عرضها
our signature talents for entertainment.
مواهبنا المميزة في مجال الترفيه.
Where's Lady Xiyan?
أين السيدة شييان؟
Her beauty and talents
جمالها ومواهبها
should grace the opening.
ينبغي أن يزين الافتتاح.
My cousin Jifu is visiting today.
ابن عمي جيفو يزورني اليوم.
Your Highness, you know she's playful.
سموك، أنت تعرف أنها مرحة.
And Xiyan is from the Meixiang House.
و Xiyan من بيت Meixiang.
They've been chatting delightfully
لقد كانوا يتحدثون بشكل ممتع
all day long.
طوال اليوم.
They're probably exhausted now.
ربما أنهم مرهقون الآن.
Lin Jifu?
لين جيفو؟
Greetings, Your Highness.
تحياتي، صاحب السمو.
Someone will never
لن يفعل أحد ذلك أبدًا
taste this venison.
تذوق هذا لحم الغزال.
My mansion keeps no drug users.
قصري لا يحتفظ بأي متعاطي للمخدرات.
I knew you detest euphoria powder,
لقد عرفت أنك تكره مسحوق النشوة،
but dared not defy Lady Jifu.
ولكن لم يجرؤ على تحدي السيدة جيفو.
So I secretly replaced it
لذلك قمت باستبداله سرا
with sachet powder when she wasn't looking.
مع مسحوق الكيس عندما لم تكن تنظر.
If you doubt me,
إذا كنت تشك بي،
the sachet's on the table.
الكيس على الطاولة.
Have the physicians examine it.
اطلب من الأطباء فحصه.
Then why are you like this?
ثم لماذا أنت هكذا؟
I merely used pleasure house methods.
لقد استخدمت فقط أساليب بيت المتعة.
This powder mimics euphoria powder's scent,
هذا المسحوق يحاكي رائحة مسحوق النشوة،
but when heated,
ولكن عندما يتم تسخينها،
it becomes an aphrodisiac.
يصبح مثيرًا للشهوة الجنسية.
Please leave first, Your Highness.
من فضلك ارحل أولاً، صاحب السمو.
After the effects subside,
بعد أن تهدأ التأثيرات،
I'll accept punishment.
سأقبل العقاب.
Knowing it was an aphrodisiac,
مع العلم أنه كان مثيرًا للشهوة الجنسية،
why consume it?
لماذا نستهلكه؟
To avoid taking euphoria powder,
لتجنب تناول مسحوق النشوة،
or to seduce me?
أو لإغوائي؟
I can't bear your disdain.
لا أستطيع أن أتحمل ازدرائك.
My actions today...
أفعالي اليوم...
You won't blame me, will you?
لن تلومني، أليس كذلك؟
(Oh, no.)
(أوه لا.)
♪Wind comes but never stays by her side♪
♪تأتي الريح ولكنها لا تبقى بجانبها أبدًا♪
♪Like fleeting memories reborn♪
♪مثل الذكريات العابرة التي تولد من جديد♪
♪As raindrops mark passing years♪
♪كما تشير قطرات المطر إلى مرور السنين♪
♪Exiled eyes♪
♪عيون منفية♪
♪A fleeting light warmed the dark♪
♪ضوء عابر يدفئ الظلام♪
Though I long to serve you,
على الرغم من أنني أرغب في خدمتك،
I'd never use vile drugs
لن أستخدم المخدرات الدنيئة أبدًا
to tarnish your honor.
لتشويه شرفك.
It was you that night.
لقد كنت أنت تلك الليلة.
I must know
يجب أن أعرف
the complete truth of that night.
الحقيقة الكاملة لتلك الليلة.
What are you referring to?
ماذا تشير اليه؟
I saw the floral mark.
رأيت العلامة الزهرية.
You fancy the floral mark?
هل تعجبك العلامة الزهرية؟
You bathe in cold water?
هل تستحم بماء بارد؟
I am easing discomfort.
أنا أخفف من الانزعاج.
The imperial physician must have a harmless remedy.
يجب أن يكون لدى الطبيب الإمبراطوري علاج غير ضار.
I don't want
أنا لا أريد
to make it known to everyone.
لجعله معروفًا للجميع.
I'll have ginger broth prepared.
سأقوم بإعداد مرق الزنجبيل.
She clearly consumed euphoria powder.
من الواضح أنها تناولت مسحوق النشوة.
Yet His Highness kept her
ومع ذلك فقد أبقاها سموه
and stayed in her chamber so long.
وبقيت في غرفتها لفترة طويلة.
I only drugged him once.
لقد أعطيته مخدرًا مرة واحدة فقط.
Now he treats me with constant coldness.
والآن يعاملني ببرود دائم.
Yuanjin,
يوانجين،
give me the powder.
أعطني المسحوق.
I want to see
أريد أن أرى
how long Pei Ji will tolerate her.
إلى متى سوف يتحملها باي جي؟
If she acts deranged after taking it,
إذا تصرفت باضطراب بعد تناوله،
revealing her hideous nature,
تكشف عن طبيعتها البشعة،
we'll see if Pei Ji remains unbothered.
دعونا نرى ما إذا كان باي جي سيبقى غير منزعج.
No.
لا.
Forget it.
انسى ذلك.
Properly-bred ladies like us
سيدات ذوات أصول سليمة مثلنا
can never outsmart her.
لا يمكن التفوق عليها أبدًا.
Que'nu just met misfortune.
لقد التقى كوينو للتو بسوء الحظ.
I won't risk your safety.
لن أعرض سلامتك للخطر.
If anyone in this realm dares harm me,
إذا تجرأ أي شخص في هذا العالم على إيذائي،
they'll answer to the Empress Dowager.
وسوف يجيبون أمام الإمبراطورة الأرملة.
What exquisite beauty.
ما أجمل هذا الجمال.
Pity though,
من المؤسف رغم ذلك
between these brows
بين هذه الحواجب
lacks the floral adornment.
يفتقر إلى الزخارف الزهرية.
Heat it up.
سخنيها.
I thought we shared rare rapport yesterday.
اعتقدت أننا شاركنا في علاقة نادرة بالأمس.
I believed us kindred spirits.
لقد صدقتنا كأرواح متقاربة.
Who'd have guessed
من كان ليتوقع ذلك؟
you're just the Princess Consort's lapdog?
هل أنت مجرد كلب الأميرة الزوجة؟
She points,
تشير،
and you bite.
وأنت تعض.
You...
أنت...
Ye Xiyan!
يي شيان!
A mere concubine,
إلى محظياتي،
yet so arrogant.
ومع ذلك متغطرسة جداً.
Have you no sense of propriety?
هل ليس لديك أي شعور باللياقة؟
Today,
اليوم،
I'll knock out
سأضرب
your teeth one by one.
أسنانك واحدة تلو الأخرى.
Then slice your tongue inch by inch.
ثم قم بتقطيع لسانك بوصة بوصة.
Let's see how you'll court favor then.
دعونا نرى كيف ستتمكن من كسب ودهم إذن.
Forgive me, Lady Jifu.
سامحيني يا سيدتي جيفو.
These are imperial jewels
هذه هي الجواهر الإمبراطورية
for the Princess Consort to wear at the ladies' banquet.
لترتديها الأميرة قرينة الملك في مأدبة السيدات.
This emerald-feathered phoenix hairpin
دبوس الشعر هذا على شكل طائر الفينيق ذو الريش الزمردي
exudes royal magnificence.
ينضح بالروعة الملكية.
L-Lady Ye,
السيدة يي،
this...
هذا...
T-This breaches protocol.
ت-هذا ينتهك البروتوكول.
A courtesan
مومس
overstepping like this.
التجاوز مثل هذا.
You should know it's a capital offense.
يجب أن تعلم أن هذه جريمة يعاقب عليها بالإعدام.
Only you can properly carry
أنت فقط من يمكنه الحمل بشكل صحيح
this phoenix hairpin,
دبوس الشعر هذا على شكل طائر الفينيق،
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
♪I once fell into deep love♪
♪لقد وقعت في حب عميق ذات مرة♪
♪Caught in a drama of love and hate♪
♪وقعت في دراما الحب والكراهية♪
♪Trapped in self-made cages♪
♪محاصرون في أقفاص من صنعهم♪
♪To whom should I direct my questions♪
♪إلى من أوجه أسئلتي♪
♪Heal my wounds from past dreams♪
♪ شفاء جروحي من أحلام الماضي ♪
♪Fate bestowed me both joy and pain♪
♪لقد منحني القدر كل من الفرح والألم♪
♪Left me a kiss of love and hate♪
♪ترك لي قبلة من الحب والكراهية♪
♪Who will unravel my dreams so deep♪
♪من سيكشف أحلامي العميقة؟♪
♪Who will save me from this lonely place♪
♪من سينقذني من هذا المكان الوحيد♪
♪Who will give me back my lonely grace♪
♪من سيعيد لي نعمتي الوحيدة♪
♪I dare not ask the infatuated ones♪
♪لا أجرؤ على سؤال المغرمين♪
♪As the moonlight thickens♪
♪مع ازدياد كثافة ضوء القمر♪
♪What I await♪
♪ما أنتظره♪
♪Which heartless soul♪
♪أي روح بلا قلب♪
♪Love departs, hatred persists♪
♪الحب يرحل، والكراهية تبقى♪
♪I woke too soon to bygone bonds♪
♪استيقظت مبكرًا جدًا على الروابط القديمة♪
♪Forgetting the lost one in old dreams♪
♪نسيان المفقود في الأحلام القديمة♪
♪No longer waiting for estranged souls♪
♪لم يعد هناك انتظار للأرواح المنفصلة♪
♪Memories flow in the deep night♪
♪تتدفق الذكريات في الليل العميق♪
♪Illuminating lonely spirits♪
♪إضاءة الأرواح الوحيدة♪
♪Become an ordinary mortal♪
♪أصبح إنسانًا عاديًا♪
♪Next spring will open heart's doors♪
♪الربيع القادم سيفتح أبواب القلب♪
♪Not seeking a specific beloved♪
♪لا أبحث عن حبيب محدد♪
♪Gracefully embracing affections♪
♪احتضان المشاعر برشاقة♪